Sol M. Linowitz Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Haloid Xerox, Inc., 1932-1962 (Box 538-568)
  - Foreign program
    - Miscellany, 1952-1957, undated
    - Netherlands, 1953-1958, (2 folders)
    - Norway, 1951-1956
    - “Relationships between the Haloid Company Rochester and European Companies,” report by R. G. Hadingham, 1956
    - Spain, 1954-1955
    - Sweden, 1954-1958
    - Switzerland, 1955-1958
  - General office file (Box 548)
    - Coordinating Committee
      - Correspondence, 1954-1959, (7 folders)
      - Minutes of meetings, 1954-1958
      - Miscellany, 1954-1956, (2 folders)
    - Cost Reduction Committee, 1956-1959, (3 folders) (Box 549)
    - F. B. Turck & Co., consultants, 1954-1956
    - Fellowships, professorships, and scholarships, 1952-1958, undated, (2 folders)
    - General correspondence
      - 1948-1954, (7 folders)
      - 1955-1958, (8 folders) (Box 550)
    - Haloid Xerox Management Group, 1956-1959
    - Ideas submitted
      - Agreement form, 1956-1958, undated
      - Correspondence, 1949-1958, (3 folders)
    - Insurance, 1953-1958
    - Labor relations (Box 551)
      - Contracts, 1939-1960, (5 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1937-1958, (3 folders)
      - Supplemental agreement, 1954-1957
      - Workers' compensation, 1958
    - Miscellany, 1949, 1956-1958, undated
    - Name changed from Haloid Co. to Haloid Xerox Inc., 1954-1958, (4 folders) (Box 552)
    - Organization of Haloid Co., 1956
    - Public relations
      - “Copyrama” promotion, 1958-1961, (3 folders)
      - General correspondence, 1948-1958, (5 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1957-1958 (Box 553)
  - Government contracts
    - Air Force
      - Air Research and Development Command
        - Variable contrast photographic papers, 1957-1958
        - Xerographic aerial photography and air-to-ground facsimile transmission, 1956, undated
      - Armour Research Foundation, Illinois Institute of Technology, Chicago, Ill., 1955-1956, 1962
      - Brooks Research, Inc., 1958
      - Cambridge Research Center, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass.
        - High temperature complex component development, 1958-1962
        - Inertia-less recording, 1956, 1962
        - Infrared image recording and display device, 1958-1962
        - Printed circuits and components1956-1962
      - International Telegraph and Telephone Corp., 1958
      - Lincoln Laboratory, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Mass.
        - Continuous output printer, 1956-1957
        - Subcontracts
          - Agreements, 1957-1959
          - Correspondence, 1958
        - Xerographic radar recording-projecting system, 1952-1962
      - Mellon Institute of Industrial Research, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1955-1958
      - Melpar, Inc., 1958 (Box 554)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1948-1958, (3 folders)
      - Negative titling, 1954-1962
      - Philco Corp., 1954-1958, (2 folders)
      - Rome Air Development Center, Griffiss Air Force Base, N.Y.
        - Flat solid-state display device, 1958
        - Generation of bright data display, 1958
        - Minicard viewer processor, 1955-1958
      - Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, Ohio
        - Aerial reconnaissance electronic reader, 1956-1957
        - Aerial strip camera, 1950-1961
        - Cameras, 1952
        - Continuous electrostatic microfilm enlarging printer, 1957-1962
        - Digital converting apparatus, 1958-1962
        - Electronic teleprinter
          - Contracts and proposals, 1955-1957, (2 folders)
          - Correspondence, 1956-1959, (3 folders) (Box 555)
        - Instantaneous recording of information pulses, 1958-1962
        - Microfilm enlarger, 1956-1959
        - Microfilm viewer processor, 1956, 1962
        - Oster photographic process, 1958-1962
        - Photo-conductive radiation detectors, 1956, 1962
        - Photo-paper processing machine, 1957-1962
        - Plate research, 1955, 1962
        - Printer processor, 1955-1957
        - Printer, projection, photographic quotation, 1957
        - Radarscope images, 1952-1956, 1962
        - Recording radar images, 1954-1962
        - Solid-state image intensifier, 1956-1962
        - Xerographic magazine for camera, 1953-1962
    - Army (Box 556)
      - Contracts, 1951-1957, (5 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1948-1958, (6 folders)
      - Proposals, 1951-1958 (Box 557)
    - Defense Department
      - Correspondence, 1951-1958, (5 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1956, undated
    - Joint Committee on Printing, U.S. Congress
      - Correspondence, 1948-1958, (7 folders)
      - Drafts of memoranda and letters, 1956, (2 folders) (Box 558)
      - Miscellany, 1954-1956, undated
    - Miscellany, 1950-1956
    - Navy
      - Claim for relief
        - Application, 1957
        - Correspondence, 1953-1958, (2 folders)
        - Miscellany, 1954-1956, undated
      - General correspondence, 1948-1958, (4 folders)
      - High-speed panchromatic xerographic plate, 1958 (Box 559)
      - Microfilm enlarger, 1958
      - Miscellany, 1951-1957
      - Recording and projection of television displays, 1958-1959
    - Signal Corps, U. S. Army
      - Continuous-tone electrostatic electrophotography, 1954-1958
      - Electrographic processor, 1955
      - Facsimile recording medium
        - Correspondence, 1956-1958
        - Proposals, 1950-1958, (2 folders)
      - General correspondence
        - 1947-1948
        - 1949-1958, (7 folders) (Box 560)
      - Graham, Savage and Associates, 1958
      - KA-9 camera, 1955-1956
      - Meeting summaries, 1947-1948
      - Microfilm enlarger, 1956-1957, (2 folders)
      - Miscellaneous agreements, contracts, and proposals
        - 1947-1948, (2 folders)
        - 1949-1950, 1958, undated, (3 folders) (Box 561)
      - Moving window display device, 1958
      - Offset plate maker and enlarger, 1957, (2 folders)
      - Real-time display recorder, 1957
      - TESI radarscope, 1956
      - Ultrathin inorganic films, 1958-1959
  - Patent and licensing file
    - Radio Corporation of America
      - Correspondence
        - 1948, Nov.-1951, June, (2 folders)
        - 1951, July-1953, Dec., (9 folders) (Box 562)
      - Miscellany, 1950-1960, undated, (2 folders)
      - Printed matter, 1954-1957, undated
      - United States v. Radio Corporation of America, 1932, 1954
    - Raytheon Co., 1950
    - Readex Microprint Corp., 1958
    - Recordak Corp. (Box 563)
      - Correspondence, 1958, (4 folders)
      - Drafts of agreements, 1955-1956, undated, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1955-1956, undated
    - Remington Rand
      - Correspondence, 1949-1958, (2 folders)
      - Drafts of agreements, 1955
    - Reproduction Products Co.
      - Correspondence, 1956-1958, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1947-1957, undated
    - Robertson Photo-Mechanix, 1955-1958, (2 folders)
    - Robillard, Jean, 1956-1957 (Box 564)
    - Royal Blueprint Co., 1957-1958
    - Royal McBee Corp., 1949-1958
    - S. D. Warren Co.1956-1958
    - Schlumberger Well Surveying Corp., 1956-1958
    - Standard Register Co., 1949-1958, (5 folders)
    - State governments
      - California, 1950-1956
      - Michigan, 1949
      - New York, 1955-1957
    - Stromberg-Carlson Co.
      - Correspondence
        - 1955-1957, (4 folders)
        - 1958, (4 folders) (Box 565)
      - Drafts of agreements, 1956, undated
      - Printed matter, 1958-1959, undated
      - Proposals for printers, 1957-1958
    - Technicolor Corp., 1955-1957, (3 folders)
    - Teletype Corp.
      - Correspondence, 1957-1958, (3 folders)
      - Drafts of agreements, 1958
      - Reports, 1959, (2 folders) (Box 566)
    - Terrytoons, Inc., 1958
    - Truline Process Co., 1955-1957
    - UARCO, Inc.
      - Correspondence, 1958
      - Miscellany, 1957-1958
    - United Merchants and Manufacturers
      - Correspondence, 1950-1957, (2 folders)
      - Drafts of agreements, 1950-1952
    - Upson Co.
      - Correspondence, 1954-1956, (2 folders)
      - Drafts of agreements, 1955
    - Vectron, Inc. (Box 567)
      - Correspondence, 1954-1957
      - Drafts of agreements, 1955-1956
    - Watland, Inc., 1956
    - Western Electric Co.
      - Correspondence, 1948-1958, (7 folders)
      - Drafts of agreements, 1949-1954, undated
    - Westinghouse Electric Corp., 1954-1958
    - Zenith Radio Corp., 1955-1956, (2 folders) (Box 568)
    - Zinsser and Co., 1954
- Speeches and Writings File, 1922-1998 (Box 568-627)
  - Part A, 1922-1966 (Box 568-577)
    Articles, book proposals, interviews, reviews, speeches, statements, and notes created prior to Linowitz's appointment as ambassador to the Organization of American States in 1966.
    Arranged alphabetically by type of material, topic, or title.
    - By Linowitz (Box 568)
      - Articles and speeches
        - Antitrust, 1956-1962, undated, (8 folders)
        - Asia, 1956-1962, undated, (4 folders)
        - Civil Rights, 1963-1966, undated (Box 569)
        - Education, 1951-1966, undated, (25 folders)
        - Europe, 1950-1955, undated, (6 folders) (Box 570)
        - Government, 1947-1966, undated, (26 folders)
        - Israel, 1947-1962, undated, (5 folders)
        - Law, 1940-1962, undated, (12 folders) (Box 571)
        - Miscellaneous, 1948-1966, undated
          - A-O, (20 folders)
          - P-R, (7 folders) (Box 572)
          - S, (5 folders); (4 folders) (Box 573)
          - T-Y, (11 folders)
        - Travel, 1955-1965, (7 folders)
        - United Nations, 1949-1966, undated
          - A, (2 folders)
          - D-U, (12 folders) (Box 574)
        - Xerox Corp., 1957-1966, undated
          - A-M, (10 folders)
          - N-X, (15 folders) (Box 575)
      - Book proposals (Box 576)
        - Correspondence, 1965-1966
        - Miscellany, 1965-1969, undated
        - “The Obligation Not to Remain Silent,” collected writings
          - Drafts 1965-1966, undated, (6 folder); (1 folder) (Box 577)
      - Book reviews, 1955-1956, undated
      - Interviews, 1962-1966, (5 folders)
    - By others, 1922, 1952-1966, undated, (2 folders)
  - Part B, 1954-1998 (Box 578-627)
    Articles, books in various stages of production, book proposals, interviews, reviews, speeches, statements, notes, and an oral history created after Linowitz's appointment as ambassador to the Organization of American States in 1966.
    Arranged in a book file, chronological file, and an oral history.
    - By Linowitz (Box 578)
      - Book file
        - The Betrayed Profession (1994)
          - Drafts
            - Early chapters, 1991-1993, (2 folders)
            - First complete version, 1993, (2 folders)
            - Revisions, 1993, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 579)
            - Final version
              - Copy A, undated, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 580)
              - Copy B, 1993, (4 folders)
          - Notes and comments, 1993, undated
          - Source material, 1954, 1981-1991, undated, (2 folders)
        - The Making of a Public Man (1985)
          - Correspondence
            - General, 1985-1992
              - A-D
              - E-Z, (4 folders) (Box 581)
            - Publisher, 1985-1988
          - Drafts
            - Copy A, chapters 1-5, undated, (2 folders)
            - Copy B, chapters 1-5, undated, (2 folders)
            - Copy C, chapters 1-5, undated, (2 folders) (Box 582)
            - Copy D, chapters 1-5, undated, (2 folders)
            - Copy E, 1985, undated, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 583)
            - Copy F, undated, (3 folders)
            - Copy G, 1985-1986, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 584)
            - Miscellaneous, 1984, undated, (2 folders)
          - Galley proofs
            - Copy A, 1985, (2 folders)
            - Copy B, 1985, (2 folders) (Box 585)
          - Lists of recipients of books, 1985-1986, undated
          - Notes, undated
          - Promotional material, 1983-1986, undated
          - Proposed outline, undated
          - Reviews, 1985-1987, undated
        - Proposed book on Latin America, 1967-1979, undated, (2 folders)
      - Chronological file (Box 586)
        - 1957, June
        - 1965, July 15-1967, May 23, (25 folders)
        - 1967, May 24-Oct. 17, (22 folders) (Box 587)
        - 1967, Oct. 19-1968, Feb. 4 See also Classified, (19 folders) (Box 588)
        - 1968, Feb. 6-May 16 See also Classified, (25 folders) (Box 589)
        - 1968, May 22-Nov. 22, (28 folders) (Box 590)
        - 1968, Dec. 4-1971, Jan. 25, (25 folders) (Box 591)
        - 1971, Apr. 2-1975, Feb. 13, (32 folders) (Box 592)
        - 1975, Mar. 10-1976, Feb. 5, (16 folders) (Box 593)
        - 1976, Feb. 17-May 23, (17 folders) (Box 594)
        - 1976, May 24-1977, Apr. 2, (12 folders) (Box 595)
        - 1977, Apr. 8-Dec. 12, (25 folders) (Box 596)
        - 1978, May 9-1980, Jan. 17, (20 folders) (Box 597)
        - 1980, Apr. 20-1981, Jan. 8, (20 folders) (Box 598)
        - 1981, Jan. 13-June 26, (18 folders) (Box 599)
        - 1981, July 21-1982, May 5, (17 folders) (Box 600)
        - 1982, May 17-Sept. 13, (14 folders) (Box 601)
        - 1982, Sept. 23-1983, Apr. 17, (11 folders) (Box 602)
        - 1983, Apr. 25-Sept. 14, (17 folders) (Box 603)
        - 1983, Sept. 18-1984, Apr. 9, (17 folders) (Box 604)
        - 1984, Apr. 12-Aug. 24, (18 folders) (Box 605)
        - 1984, Sept. 16-Nov. 15, (16 folders) (Box 606)
        - 1984, Nov. 23-1985, May 7, (13 folders) (Box 607)
        - 1985, May 29-Nov. 12, (13 folders) (Box 608)
        - 1985, Nov. 14-1986, June 10, (18 folders) (Box 609)
        - 1986, June 12-Nov. 21, (14 folders) (Box 610)
        - 1986, Dec. 10-1987, Apr. 23, (13 folders) (Box 611)
        - 1987, Apr. 28-Oct. 29, (13 folders) (Box 612)
        - 1987, Nov. 2-1988, Apr. 24, (11 folders) (Box 613)
        - 1988, May 26-Oct. 22, (9 folders) (Box 614)
        - 1988, Oct. 29-1989, May 5, (12 folders) (Box 615)
        - 1989, May 18-Aug. 23, (12 folders) (Box 616)
        - 1989, Sept. 27-Nov. 27, (7 folders) (Box 617)
        - 1989, Dec. 13-1990, Apr. 11, (8 folders) (Box 618)
        - 1990, May 10-Oct. 12, (8 folders) (Box 619)
        - 1990, Oct. 20-1991, May 31, (10 folders) (Box 620)
        - 1991, June 7-Nov. 16, (10 folders) (Box 621)
        - 1991, Dec. 5-1992, June 8, (7 folders) (Box 622)
        - 1992, June 23-1993, June 26, (12 folders) (Box 623)
        - 1993, July 19-1997, Dec. 3, (6 folders) (Box 624)
        - Undated, (1 folder) (Box 625)
      - Oral history, 1982-1983, (3 folders) (Box 626)
    - By others
      - Burns, Ken (1953- ), 1985
      - Hart, Gary (1936- ), 1986, (2 folders)
      - Major, John (1936- ), 1991 (Box 627)
      - Miscellaneous, 1954-1998, undated, (5 folders)
      - Stewart, Maco (1937- ), 1990
- Miscellany, 1923-1995 (Box 628-638)
  Biographical material, clippings, legal files, photographs, scrapbooks, and memorabilia.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material, name of person or organization, or topic and therein chronologically.
  - Address lists, undated (Box 628)
  - Awards, 1956-1983, (4 folders)
  - Biographical material, 1960-1991, undated, (5 folders)
  - Clippings
    - Abstracts from New York Times Information Service, 1969-1983
    - Miscellaneous, 1951-1993, undated
  - Financial records, 1948-1976, (2 folders) (Box 629)
  - Law school
    - Correspondence, 1937-1938
    - Notes, undated, (2 folders)
  - Legal files
    - Miscellany
    - Office of Price Administration (Box 630)
      - Cases
        - Index, 1942-1944
        - 315 W. 97th St. Realty Co. v. Porter
          - Briefs and transcripts, 1944-1946
          - Oral argument, 1946
          - Reports, 1945-1946, undated, (2 folders)
        - Shaker Parkway Co. v. Porter (Box 631)
          - Briefs and transcripts, 1946
          - Miscellany, 1943-1946, undated
          - Oral argument, 1946
        - Others
          - A-G, 1942-1946, undated, (2 folders)
          - H-W, 1942-1946, undated, (3 folders) (Box 632)
      - Miscellany, 1943-1949, undated
      - Notes, outlines, and background material, 1943-1946, undated, (3 folders) (Box 633)
      - Oral arguments before U.S. Emergency Court of Appeals, 1943
        - Avant v. Brown
        - Chatlos v. Brown
        - Gale Realty Co. v. Brown
        - Madison Park Corp. v. Brown
        - Northwood Apartments. v. Brown
        - Spaeth v. Brown
    - Sutherland and Sutherland (law firm), cases
      - In re First Trust and Deposit Co., 1941, undated
      - Metropolitan Life Ins. Co. v. Union Trust Co. of Rochester, 1941, undated (Box 634)
      - Miscellany, 1940, undated
      - In re Shay, 1941-1942
      - Tollin v. Nordseth, 1942, undated
  - Memorabilia, 1931-1986, undated, (3 folders)
  - Notes and fragments, undated, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 635)
  - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy, photocopies of her letters to Linowitz and of a drawing, undated See also Oversize
  - Passports and visas, 1963-1982, (2 folders)
  - Photographs
    - Miscellany, 1963-1995
    - Portraits, 1966-1982, undated
    - White House
      - Carter, Jimmy, administration, 1978-1980, undated
      - Johnson, Lyndon B., administration, 1967-1969 See Oversize
  - Scrapbooks
    - Set I
      - 1923-1981
      - 1948-1955
      - 1956-1960, (1 folder) (Box 636)
      - 1962, (2 folders)
      - 1965
      - 1966
      - 1967
        - Vol. I, (2 folders)
        - Vol II (Box 637)
      - 1969, (2 folders)
      - 1971, (2 folders)
      - 1977 (Box 638)
      - 1978
      - 1985
    - Set II
      - China, 1979 See Oversize
      - Japan, undated See Oversize
      - Mexico, 1965 See Oversize
      - Miscellany See Oversize
        - 1945-1993
        - 1951-1966
      - Organization of American States See Oversize
        - Vol. 1, 1966-1969
        - Vol. 2, 1967, Apr.-Aug.
        - Vol. 3, 1967, Aug.-Nov.
        - Vol. 4, 1967, Nov.-Dec.
        - Vol. 5, 1967, Dec.-1968, Feb.
        - Vol. 6, 1968, Feb.-June
        - Vol. 7, 1968, July-1969, Apr.
        - Vol. 8, foreign language, 1967-1968
      - Panama Canal, 1977-1978 See Oversize
        - Vol. 1
        - Vol. 2
  - Sketch of Linowitz, 1966
  - Social events, 1968-1983, undated, (2 folders)
- Addition, 1934-1999 (Box 639-650)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, schedules and itineraries, speeches and writings, notes, legal files, programs, biographical material, photographs, news clippings, and other printed matter complementing the contents of other series and spanning many phases of Linowitz’s career. The bulk of the series consists of file copies and some drafts of speeches, articles, and other writings.
  Arranged as general correspondence, subject file, personal file, and speeches and writings and therein chronologically or alphabetically by name, topic, or type of material.
  - General correspondence, 1962-1993, (4 folders) (Box 639)
  - Subject file
    - Court of Public Opinion (television program), 1951-1955
    - Governor of New York, possible candidate, 1965-1966, (4 folders)
    - Haiti, 1994
    - International Executive Service Corps, 1952, 1963-1965
    - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1961-1966
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1964-1966
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1964-1966 (Box 640)
    - Legal profession, reflections on, 1962-1974, 1988-1993
    - Memoranda for the file, 1955-1957, 1966, 1975-1981, undated
    - Notes, miscellaneous, 1966, undated
    - Office of Price Administration
      - Briefs, 1943-1946, (2 folders)
      - Outlines of oral arguments, 1942-1946
    - Panama Canal Treaty
      - Conflict of financial interest opinions, 1977
      - "How We Got the Treaty," undated
      - Invitations and news clippings, 1977
    - Rochester, N.Y., 1955-1958, 1965 (Box 641)
    - Sadat, Anwar, 1981
    - Special Committee on Campus Tensions, final report, 1970, (2 folders)
    - Time, Inc., newstour of the Middle East, Morocco, and Algeria, 1974-1975, 1981
    - United States Navy, Bureau of Yards and Docks, Office of General Counsel, 1945
    - Washington, D.C., file
      - Appointments and travel vouchers, 1957-1963
      - Notes and schedules, 1965-1966, undated
      - Printed matter, 1964-1966
    - Woman's National Democratic Club, Washington, D.C., 1971-1977, undated
    - Xerox Corporation, 1961-1965, undated
  - Personal file
    - Biographical material, 1963-1989
    - College and high school, 1934-1935, 1970, 1981
    - Early script for a performance, Temple B'rith Kodesh, Rochester, N.Y., undated
    - Eulogy, Rose Oglenskye Linowitz (mother), undated (Box 642)
    - Honors and tributes, 1967, 1976, 1983, 1996
    - News clippings, 1952-1989, (3 folders)
    - Photographs, 1966-1967, undated
    - Printed matter, 1946-1947, 1965, 1981
  - Speeches and writings
    - Binder Set A
      - Vol. II
        - Interviews, 1965-1966
        - Israel, 1957
        - Legal, 1951-1963
        - Miscellaneous, circa 1946-1966, (2 folders)
      - Vol. III
        - Trips, 1958-1965
        - United Nations, 1949-1966 (Box 643)
        - Xerox Corporation, 1958-1966
    - Binder Set B
      - Nos. 1-65, 1966, Nov.-1968, Oct., (5 folders)
      - Nos. 66-83, 1968, Oct.-1969, Apr., (2 folders) (Box 644)
    - Binder Set C
      - Vol. 1, 1969, May-1971, Feb., (4 folders)
      - Vol. 2, 1971, Feb.-Apr.
      - Vol. 2, 1971, May-1972, Aug., (4 folders) (Box 645)
      - Vol. 3, 1972, Dec.-1975, Nov., (4 folders)
      - Vol. 4, 1976, Jan.-1978, Dec., (3 folders) (Box 646)
      - Vol. 5, 1979, Jan.-1980, Nov., (3 folders)
      - Vol. 6, 1981, Jan.-1982, Oct., (5 folders) (Box 647)
      - Vol. 7, 1983, Apr.-Sept., (2 folders)
      - Vol. 7, 1983, Oct. (Box 648)
    - Binder Set D, Vols. 1-3, 1984, Mar.-1987, Nov., (7 folders)
    - Loose copies, 1940-1992, (10 folders) (Box 649)
    - Loose copies, 1993-1999, undated, (3 folders) (Box 650)
- Classified, 1962-1982 (Box CL 1-CL 3)
  Correspondence, memoranda, and reports.
  Arranged and described according to the series, containers, and folders from which the items were removed.
  - Government Service (Box CL 1)
    - Organization of American States
      - Official file
        - Alliance for Progress
          - Funding cuts, 1968 (Container 96)
        - Chile, 1968 (Container 97)
        - Johnson, Lyndon B., and White House staff, 1967 (Containers 99-100 ), (2 folders)
        - Katzenbach, Nicholas deB., 1967 (Container 100)
        - Military governments, 1967-1969 (Container 100)
        - Miscellany
          - Classified documents, 1966-1969 (Container 100)
        - “O” miscellaneous, 1967 (Container 102)
        - Panama, 1968 (Container 102)
        - Peru, 1969 (Container 102)
        - Plaza, Galo, 1968 (Container 102)
        - Rusk, Dean, 1967-1968 (Container 103)
        - United Nations
          - Correspondence, 1967 (Container 105)
        - Venezuela, 1967 (Container 106)
    - Panama Canal Treaties
      - Carter, Jimmy, and White House staff, 1977 (Container 113)
      - General correspondence, 1976-1977, undated (Containers 117-118 ), (4 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1977 (Container 119), (2 folders)
      - Reagan, Ronald, 1977 (Container 121)
      - Sea level canal proposal, 1977 (Container 121)
      - Treaties
        - Drafts, 1977, undated (Container 122), (4 folders)
    - Middle East Peace Negotiations
      - Appointment and confirmation, 1979 (Container 123)
      - Carter, Jimmy, and White House staff, 1980 (Container 126)
      - Clippings
        - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Container 127)
      - General correspondence, 1977-1980 (Container 128), (4 folders)
      - Israel, 1980 (Container 129) (Box CL 2)
      - Israeli settlements in occupied territories, 1980 (Container 129)
      - Jerusalem, 1979, undated (Container 129)
      - Memorandum of understanding, 1980, undated (Container 129)
      - Negotiation talking points, 1980, undated (Container 130)
      - Office staff and functions, 1979 (Container 130)